SAMUEL ROBINSON

User Experience Designer who is just beginning his incredible journey in the field of UX. Third year student at Wilfrid Laurier University, working towards my bachelor of design (B.Des). It is my mission to advocate for the needs of everyday, normal people.

EXPERIENCE

User Experience Intern @ Sherpa UX Los Angeles, CA

May 2021 - September 2021

- · participated in meetings to discuss project plans
- designed (from wireframe to final mockup) and tested multiple main screens using Adobe XD, which made up the whole user experience of a music streaming app
- Developed feedback systems for login and similar interactions
- participated in team meetings in order to advise app developers of best UX practises
- conducted user testing and analysis in order to learn pain points and areas for improvement
- iterated app usability using research findings
- helped to develop the most important aspects of the backend admin panel
- will be back once the app has been released in order to maintain frequent updates including haptics and usability improvements

Student of User Experience Design @ WLU Toronto, ON

2019 - present

- participated in multiple major group projects
- served as team lead on mulitple occasions to guide the team towards success
- undertook user research, mapping, wireframing, prototyping, user-testing, and iteration, and all aspects of the design thinking process
- sucesfully presented solutions to the class, professor, and clients
- · won awards for outstanding work

EDUCATION

Wilfrid Laurier University

2019-2023

Bachelor of Design (B.Des), User Experience Design

sam.r.i@live.com (226) 922 9507 www.samuelrobinson.ca Toronto, ON, Canada

COURSES

Design Thinking 1 & 2
Digital Technology Lab
Graphic Design Studio 1 & 2
UX Strategy
Interaction Design 1 & 2
Maker Lab 1 & 2
Web Design Lab 1 & 2
Trends in UX
Information Design
Design of Immersive Spaces
Research in UX
Mobile App Design Lab

TOOLS

Adobe XD
Adobe Illustrator
Adobe Premiere Pro
Adobe InDesign
Google Suite
Miro
OptimalSort
Wordpress
Github
Sketch
HTML
CSS

SKILLS

Team Leadership
Wireframing/Prototyping
User Testing
UI Design
User Research
Journey/Empathy Mapping
Design Thinking
Implementing Feedback
Responsibility
Quick Learning
Self-Motivation